syedbalkhi.com 2010-05-03

# Privacy Policy www.syedbalkhi.com

* * *

**Privacy Policy**

* * *

This website offers a number of features which may include a bulletin board / message forum, website directory, classified ads, and/or products for sale. 

This website does store some information in "cookies" on your computer. It does not store any personally identifible information in cookies, unless you use a section of our website that requires a login, your login information (email address) may be stored in a cookie for the duration of your browser session. If you participate in the forums cookies will be used to help prevent abusive and repeat postings. If you disable cookies, our website may not function properly. 

If you participate in any bulletin board, forum, blog or directory listing on our website, any information you provide in the submission for publication may be displayed for everyone to see. If you post on our bulletin board your IP address may also be displayed. 

If you submit a listing to our directory, all of the information except for your email address will be displayed for everyone to see. Your email address will only be used to contact you directly regarding your submission (ie: to send your account password and information about approval of your listings). 

If you submit a classified ad all of the information except for your email address will be displayed for everyone to see (including the email address you specify in your classified ad). Your email address will only be used to contact you directly regarding your submission (ie: to send your account password and information about approval of your listings). 

Emails we might send you:

  * When you register on our site, we will send you an acknowledgement email with your password. 
  * When you request your password be resent to you. 
  * When you specificially subscribe to a notification, ie: to be notified by email when you are sent an internal email. You must have already registered on our site. You can subscribe and unscribe to notificaitons from our member page. 
  * When you submit a listing to our directory, a guest blog post, question/answer or other section. We may email you telling you your posting has been approved, declined or asking a question about it. 

If you make use of any section of our website that requires payment (ie: premium listings, or paid advertisements) we will collect the information necessary to conduct the transaction and that information may be shared with our vendors, contractors, etc only as necessary to complete the transaction. If you participate in a fraudulent transcation, attempt to, or abuse the services or network resources any and all information we have or can collect may be shared with anyone we feel is necessary to resolve the problem. 

Any products listed for sale are from independent websites and you must check directly with them regarding their provide policies. Although we regularly update the product information, you should check directly with the vendor to confirm prices and other product information. 

If you click a link that takes you off this site, you must check with that site for its privacy policy. 

Home Page

Cookies: If you login on our site, we store a cookie to save your email and encrypted password while you are logged in. We do not store other personally identifible information in cookies. We store non-personally identifiable information cookies to save various settings and prevent multiple and spam postings. 

Cookies and our advertisers: Advertisers on our website may set cookies and you should refer directly to an advertisers website for details on their cookies and privacy policy. Their cookies may be set while you surf our site, by virtue of the advertisement being placed in an iframe. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, your need to contact them directly. 

"DoubelClick Dart Cookie". Some of our pages may display advertisements provided by Google. Please note the following information with respect to this: 

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

* * *

DMCA Notification and Procedure for Making Claims of Copyright Infringement

* * *

GLR Sales, LLC will process notices of alleged infringement which it receives and will take appropriate actions as required by the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (the "DMCA") and other applicable intellectual property laws. Pursuant to the DMCA, notifications of claimed copyright infringement should be sent to the Designated Agent. 

Name/Contact Information of Designated Agent:   
Glen Roberts   
E-mail: dmca at glrsales.com   
Fax: 408-228-0566   
Mailing Address: PO Box 12148, Localidad 4, Montevideo, URUGUAY 11300 

To be effective, the notification must be in writing and contain the following information (DMCA, 17 U.S.C. 512(c)(3)): 

1\. a physical or electronic signature of the person authorized to act on behalf the copyright owner;   
2\. identification or description of the copyrighted work you claim has been infringed;   
3\. identification or description of the work you believe is infringing on your copyrighted work and enough information to assist GLR Sales, LLC in locating the allegedly infringing work;   
4\. your address, telephone number, and email address;   
5\. a statement that you have a good faith belief that the use by the person you believe has infringed on your copyright is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law;   
6\. your statement, made under penalty of perjury, that the information contained in your notification is accurate, and that you are the copyright owner or are authorized to act on the owner's behalf. 

**Notes:** Allfeeds.org is a directory of RSS Feeds. If an RSS Feed contains your work without your permission it is best to contact the publisher of the RSS Feed directly. When the publisher of the feed updates or changes their feed, those changes will automatically be reflect on allfeeds.org and other websites that may use the feed. 

If you are the publisher of an RSS feed which is listed on allfeeds.org and you do not want it listed, the fastest way to have it removed is to use our [delete feed](http://www.allfeeds.org/delete.html) process which will instantly remove it for any reason. If you instead prefer to use the DCMA procedure make sure you sufficiently identify the feed for us to locate it. 

* * *  
  
Web site copyright (c) 2009-2010 GLR Sales LLC.
